{
    "id": "c6d431c882c84f54b59be929fe239495",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am waiting …………………….. a call from my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t agree ………………………… your opinion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can never count ……………………… selfish people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs ………………………. a martial clan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is full ……………………… ambition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of people die …………………………. malaria.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him ………………………… the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have made dinner ………………………….. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married ………………………….. her childhood friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you agree …………………………. the argument that smoking should be banned in public places?",
            "description": "We agree with a view, opinion, argument or policy. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good ………………………….. fooling people.",
            "description": "We say good or bad at.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone praised the girl ……………………….. her honesty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}